rock.in 2012-12-17

# Privacy Policy

**Your Privacy**

“www.rock.in” / “RockIn” / “Rock.in" and its affiliates are totally committed to protecting the privacy of our site visitors and customers. The Rock.in team fully appreciates and respects the importance of privacy on the Internet. We will not disclose information about our customers to third parties except where it is part of providing a service to you - e.g. arranging for a product to be sent to you, carrying out credit and other security checks and for the purposes of customer research and profiling or where we have your express permission to do so. By accessing the services provided by Rock.in you agree to the collection and use of your data by Rock.in in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy.

Note: Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically.

**Your Consent**

We will not sell your name, address, e-mail address, credit card information or personal information to any third party (excluding partners from whom you may have linked to our site) without your permission.

**We may collect the following personally identifiable information about you:**

  * Name including first and last name.
  * Alternate email address.
  * Mobile phone number and contact details.
  * ZIP/Postal code.
  * Financial information (like account or credit card numbers)
  * Opinions of features on our websites.
  * Other information as per our registration proces.

**We may also collect the following information:**

  * About the pages you visit/access.
  * The links you click on our site.
  * The number of times you access the page.
  * The number of times you have shopped on our web site.
  * Details pertaining to your family members, birthdays, anniversaries etc.

You can terminate your account at any time. However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or the termination of your account.

**Communication & Marketing**

If you have made a purchase from our website we may occasionally update you on our latest products, news and special offers via e-mail, post & telephone. You will also be given the opportunity to receive such communications from us and selected third parties when you become a member of Rock.in

When you register, you will be given the option to opt-out of subscribing to our regular update service which will send you:

At all times, we will offer you the opportunity to unsubscribe out of any service or update to which you have subscribed, if you change your mind. Any e-mail we send you will contain an easy automated unsubscribe link so that you can opt-out of that particular mailshot. Simply follow the indications in the e-mail. Alternatively you can change your email preferences or opt out of all emails by logging into My Account.

**What are Cookies?**

A cookie is a small information file that is sent to your computer and is stored on your hard drive. If you have registered with us then your computer will store an identifying cookie which will save you time each time you re-visit Rock.in, by remembering your email address for you. You can change the settings on your browser to prevent cookies being stored on your computer without your explicit consent. If you choose not to receive cookies, you may still use most of the features of our website, including the ability to purchase items

**Site Statistics  **

We may disclose aggregate, anonymised statistics about the number of visitors to this Website or number of purchases made as required by our investors. We use an independent measurement and research company to gather data regarding the visitors to this Website on our behalf using cookies and code which is embedded in the site. Both the cookies and the embedded code provide statistical information about visits to pages on the site, the duration of individual page view, paths taken by visitors through the site, data on visitors' screen settings and other general information.

Rock.in uses and stores this type of information, as with that obtained from other cookies used on the site, to help it improve the services to its users. Further information regarding the way in which this information is obtained and used can be obtained by contacting us at [care@rock.in](mailto:care@rock.in)

**Protecting your security**

We may use personal information provided by you in order to conduct appropriate anti-fraud checks. Personal information that you provide may be disclosed to a credit reference or fraud prevention agency, which may keep a record of that information. This is done only to confirm your identity - a credit check is not performed and your credit rating is unaffected.

**Transfers of your Information**

The information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside India. It may also be processed by staff operating out of India who work for Rock.in or one of our suppliers. Such processing may, for example, be required in order to fulfil your order, process your payment details or provide support services.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. We will do our best to protect your personal data, but cannot guarantee the security of data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

**Disclosures of your information**

We may disclose your personal information to any of our group of companies. We may also disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * In the event that Rock.in sells or buys any business or assets.
  * If Rock.in or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data which we hold about our customers may be one of the transferred assets
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Rock.in, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Third party sites**

Our site may contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and other third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that they have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

**Checking your Details**

If you wish to verify the details you have submitted to Rock.in you may do so by contacting us via the e-mail address or address given below. Our security procedures mean that we may request proof of identity before we reveal information. This proof of identity will take the form of your e-mail address and password submitted upon registration. You must therefore keep this information safe as you will be responsible for any action which we take in response to a request from someone using your e-mail and password. We would strongly recommend that you do not use the browser's password memory function as that would permit other people using your terminal to access your personal information.

Although we will endeavor to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. By using this site, you agree that we will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties.

**Contacting us**

We are always pleased to hear from our customers (even if it is a complaint!). We are always grateful for any time you spend providing us with the knowledge we need to ensure our customers are completely satisfied - we want you to return to the site and to recommend us to your friends and family. If you have any questions or feedback about this statement, or if you would like us to stop processing your information, please do not hesitate to contact a customer service member of the Rock.in team, who will be delighted to answer any questions you may have.

You can either contact [care@rock.in](mailto:care@rock.in) or,

**write to us at:**

Rock.in Studios,

A-301, Interface 16, Mindspace

Malad (W),

Mumbai - 400 064

India

**Tel** :      +91 22 40 777 555
